1. emphasize we obtained new coordinate-update algorithms for problems that were not treated with CU before

2. theoretical depth: identify the nonexpansive operator problems and then develop a CF update, based on the CF analysis of operators

3. Formal CF analysis, especially for composite operators, did not appear in the literature. Although it appears to be simple to understand, 

CU idea is long existing. Applications also long existing. And CU on these applicatoins have strong performance. Why they are not proposed or used before? Theory, ideas, applications are 脱节。

Emphasize that the journal is about both theory and applications.

Page limit does not allow us to include more theory in it.
